<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Nana.</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nana.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Luna the Little Owl and the Missing Big Branch</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752264772-luna-the-little-owl-and-the-missing-big-branch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752264772-luna-the-little-owl-and-the-missing-big-branch/</guid><description>Have you ever lost something important? Luna, the tiny owl, loves her favorite big branch in the tree. One day, it suddenly disappears. Luna needs to find out why and how she can fix the problem! Can she learn something special along the way?</description></item><item><title>The Curious Little Bird and the Big Problem</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752264231-the-curious-little-bird-and-the-big-problem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:03:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752264231-the-curious-little-bird-and-the-big-problem/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what happens when a small bird faces a big challenge? One sunny morning, a tiny bird named Pip finds his favorite nest is broken. He wants to fix it, but he doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how. Join Pip as he discovers that asking for help and sharing ideas can turn a problem into a new adventure.</description></item><item><title>Leo the Little Lion and the Lost Hat</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752263785-leo-the-little-lion-and-the-lost-hat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752263785-leo-the-little-lion-and-the-lost-hat/</guid><description>One sunny morning, Leo the Little Lion finds his favorite hat missing. Who took it, and how will he find it again? Join Leo on his fun adventure to discover kindness and honesty.</description></item><item><title>Lina and the Lost Snowflake</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752262679-lina-and-the-lost-snowflake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752262679-lina-and-the-lost-snowflake/</guid><description>Have you ever lost something special and then found it again? What if it was a snowflake that wanted to stay warm and not melt? Join Lina, a curious girl, as she discovers the magic of caring for a tiny snowflake trapped in her mitten. Will she help it stay cool or let it melt away? Find out how a simple act can turn into a beautiful lesson about kindness.</description></item><item><title>Leo the Little Lion’s Big Problem</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752262246-leo-the-little-lions-big-problem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752262246-leo-the-little-lions-big-problem/</guid><description>One day, Leo the lion cub wants to play with his friends, but he is too shy to join. What will happen when Leo finds out that being brave is easy when he just tries? Discover how Leo learns a simple trick to make friends and have fun.</description></item><item><title>The Little Turtle and the Big Splash</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752261652-the-little-turtle-and-the-big-splash/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752261652-the-little-turtle-and-the-big-splash/</guid><description>Do you wonder what happens when a small turtle tries to make a big splash? Little Turtle wants to be the fastest swimmer in the pond, but he is very shy. One day, he learns that trying your best is more important than winning. Can he find a way to have fun and be brave?</description></item><item><title>Luna and the Lost Hat</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752261247-luna-and-the-lost-hat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752261247-luna-and-the-lost-hat/</guid><description>What happens when Luna&amp;rsquo;s favorite hat goes missing? Will she find it and learn something special? Join Luna on her quiet adventure and see how a small act can bring big happiness.</description></item><item><title>The Little Rabbit and the Missing Carrot</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752260635-the-little-rabbit-and-the-missing-carrot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:03:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752260635-the-little-rabbit-and-the-missing-carrot/</guid><description>Have you ever lost something and didn’t know where to find it? Imagine a tiny rabbit who loves carrots very much but faces a puzzle when his favorite carrot disappears. Can he find it again with friends’ help? Let’s discover what happens next!</description></item><item><title>The Little Red Owl and the Lost Stars</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752260543-the-little-red-owl-and-the-lost-stars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:02:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752260543-the-little-red-owl-and-the-lost-stars/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what happens when stars fall from the sky? One night, a tiny owl named Ollie finds some lost stars on the ground. He wants to help them find their way back home. But how can a little owl do such a big thing? Join Ollie on his gentle adventure and see how kindness can light up the night.</description></item><item><title>The Little Turtle and the Big River</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752259666-the-little-turtle-and-the-big-river/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752259666-the-little-turtle-and-the-big-river/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered how a tiny turtle can cross a big, wide river? One brave little turtle faces many challenges to find a new home. Along the way, he learns that with patience and help from friends, even big problems can be solved.</description></item><item><title>The Little Turtle and the Busy Bird</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752254641-the-little-turtle-and-the-busy-bird/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:24:01 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752254641-the-little-turtle-and-the-busy-bird/</guid><description>What happens when a slow turtle and a busy bird want to run a race? Will they find a way to work together and learn something new? Join the fun as they discover that everyone has special strengths!</description></item><item><title>Timmy and the Lost Toy</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752254548-timmy-and-the-lost-toy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:22:28 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752254548-timmy-and-the-lost-toy/</guid><description>Have you ever lost something very special? What if that thing was a favorite toy and you didn’t know where it was? Join Timmy the Bunny on his adventure to find his missing car. Will he find it in time? Let’s see what happens!</description></item><item><title>The Little Bird and the Lost Feather</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752254034-the-little-bird-and-the-lost-feather/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:13:54 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752254034-the-little-bird-and-the-lost-feather/</guid><description>Have you ever lost something special? What happened when a tiny bird lost its favorite feather? Join the little bird as it goes on a small adventure to find it again. Will it be easy or tricky? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out!</description></item><item><title>Leo the Little Lion's Big Bright Idea</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752253463-leo-the-little-lions-big-bright-idea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 03:28:10 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1752253463-leo-the-little-lions-big-bright-idea/</guid><description>Have you ever done something small that made a big difference? What happens when a tiny idea turns into a big happy surprise? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out with Leo, the little lion who loves to think!</description></item><item><title>The Brave Little Squirrel</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1751037950-the-brave-little-squirrel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 03:28:10 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1751037950-the-brave-little-squirrel/</guid><description>What happens when a tiny squirrel wants to help his big friends? Can he find a way to be brave? Let’s find out in the woods!</description></item><item><title>The Little Ant's Big Journey</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1751037896-the-little-ants-big-journey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 02:48:59 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1751037896-the-little-ants-big-journey/</guid><description>Have you ever wanted to go on a big adventure? What happens when you feel small, but you have big dreams? Let’s find out how one tiny ant faced her biggest challenge.</description></item><item><title>The Little Blue Fish and the Lost Shell</title><link>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1751037922-the-little-blue-fish-and-the-lost-shell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 02:47:35 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://husnulhamidiah.github.io/nana/posts/1751037922-the-little-blue-fish-and-the-lost-shell/</guid><description>What happens when a little fish can&amp;rsquo;t find her favorite shell? Will she find it again? Let’s see what happens!</description></item></channel></rss>